<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>r on Maia Pelletier</title>
    <link>/categories/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in r on Maia Pelletier</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>pudding music challenge: comparing music knowledge 📻</title>
      <link>/post/pudding-music-challenge-comparing-music-knowledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pudding-music-challenge-comparing-music-knowledge/</guid>
      <description>First things first, I need to give away all the credit for this idea. Thanks to Namita (@nnstats on Twitter) since this blog post was fully inspired by this tweet.
had to graph my results from @puddingviz&#39;s delightful generational music challenge (https://t.co/6MBp6cdTla) and it turns out I started knowing what music was in ~2005 pic.twitter.com/AwxhPblwZd— Namita (@nnstats) May 2, 2020It was such a fun idea, I decided to do it too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pjocolors: baby&#39;s first package 📦</title>
      <link>/post/pjocolors-baby-s-first-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pjocolors-baby-s-first-package/</guid>
      <description>About a 2 weeks ago, I tweeted out that I had released my first package pjocolors, which contains 5 colour palettes based on the (original) book covers of Percy Jackson and the Olympians by Rick Riordan. Today I released the first update, complete with updated palettes and new functions for use with ggplot2📊!
I decided to develop this simple package, not so much for utility purposes (although I’ve used it in two #TidyTuesday’s now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#tidytuesday: tour de france winners 🚴</title>
      <link>/post/tidytuesday-tour-de-france-winners/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/tidytuesday-tour-de-france-winners/</guid>
      <description>For this week’s #TidyTuesday, I decided that I wanted to do an in-depth exploration of the this week’s dataset of Tour de France winners, and write a blog post about how I generally go about my data exploration for Tidy Tuesday.
However, I desperately need to preface this blog post: I went into this week’s #TidyTuesday excited to learn more about a sport I know almost nothing about. I’ve come out of it completely obsessed with the drama and insanity that is the history of the Tour de France.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>